You
Such a beautiful planet I catch my breath every time I see it
Does seeing where you were born stir any memories in you?
Slain well, um, I guess yes, no need to be embarrassed
I've only been away for two months, but I find myself missing many things about verse
Earth
The cradle in which all of humanity was born
It's always been a dream of mine to see it with my own two eyes. Oh, I see
Tell me slain they say the atmosphere there is blue as well as the oceans. I've always wondered about that
Is it actually true that on earth the air and the water have a blue tint to them?
No, the air and water are transparent
Transparent but in a thick enough layer. I understand they refract the light reflected from them
So they look blue to the eye I
Believe that is how it works
Water and air there in such vast quantities that they can bend light
That's amazing. I can't begin to imagine it
You've been in here for some time
Count curtail the hour seems to be growing quite late. Please make your way to your bed chamber now if you would
Princess of Salem
Oh dear that long has passed
Seeing things from this veranda. It is certainly easy to lose track of time
Good night slain can we continue tomorrow with my lessons about earth yes, of course as you prefer
Oh
The goodwill visit by a Salem versa Lucia of the verse Empire is now only three days away
There is a growing sense of welcome, but there are also tensions
Political observers are divided on the underlying reason for this visit by the princess royal be officially standing now
Good morning Yuki
Which would you prefer an omelet or fluffy scrambled eggs?
The omelet I guess
Sorry, but it's scrambled eggs today
Aren't you eating anything? No, I already ate oh
Yuki aren't you scheduled for drill instructor today?
Hey, I'm totally late now. Why didn't you wake me I did a dozen times warrant officer kaisuka hang on a minute
You gotta wait not to worry if you run really fast you might still make the next bus
Maybe just speaking from experience. Oh, and make sure you put the dirty dishes in the sink, okay?
I'm a heartless jerk
When the Apollo 17 mission to the moon discovered an artifact belonging to an ancient martian civilization
The hyper gate it paved the way for human colonization and development of Mars
However, this resulted in the emergence of the first empire which claimed ownership of the martian relics in old noah their ancient technology
Thus giving rise to a long-standing conflict
Good morning in a hope good morning
What's up? Why isn't yuki with you?
Dear sister overslept
But if she picks up her feet she should make it in time for the drills
Oh, no
How dare you try to shirk your duty to escort our goddess of tuesdays
Panivia
Who's that goddess of laziness laziness is hot
I mean those of us planning on a college career don't need to worry about making it to drills
Planning on going to college, huh?
As I recall oka joe you flunked your midterm tests calm. Let's get something straight
You're the one who got a c-minus on the tactical exercises
I've been taking good notes and every tiny fact I hear
I'm going to take back my title is top student in the class
You sure are primed to take you not hold down a peg or two aren't you inko?
Disaster recovery
Shinawara is still being put back together like the other areas
Heaven's fall 15 years ago
Those damn martians the bastards really went off on us didn't they?
Take my word things could be a lot worse like where nina and I come from
But aren't things getting back to normal with mars right now?
With that goodwill ambassador who's coming?
Oh, you mean that verse princess?
What's her name again?
Ase... Ise...
No wonder you flunked
Oh bite me
Oh
In 1999 the verse empire declared war against the united forces of earth
As a result of the conflict the hypergate went out of control and destroyed the moon itself
the astronomical body that had been earth's satellite for four
I apologize for being so late
Hi, warren officer sleepyhead
Lieutenant marito you're here
Ew
Lieutenant i believe i asked you to refrain from drinking on military training days
This is only just a game no need to get so serious
We're using live fire today
Master arm switch on fire control enabled lowering dampers lock on target correction and fire
All right let's switch pilots now squad B move to the bleachers you'll be the spotter warrant officer
Please sir take it easy on the drinking students start to lose respect when the teacher smells like alcohol
Don't you worry about it i'm used to being disrespected
No sir
Huh
Actually i know that you're a fine soldier lieutenant marito
Don't you worry about it i did warn you to cut back on the alcohol didn't i lieutenant
I did warn you to cut back on the alcohol didn't i lieutenant
Hello good to see you dr yagurai
It's been a while
Making a house call all the way out here are you
A patient of mine is being uncooperative
Can't drink i can't do my job for the students it was just another drill day today
You know that the work you're doing is important right
The kg6 sleip near
The cataphract developed by the ufe to combat the coming martian threat
A piloted mobile weapon
Military training is now part of their high school education
They fire that 75 mil cannon like it's just a game and then we tell them they're ready to defend the old homeland
And you say i've got an important job pumping their heads full all this crap give me a break
lieutenant
15 years ago the top brass hushed up everything that happened in tanegashima
Nobody believes me
But i know what i saw
Old noah
Out on mars they got their hands on the power of the gods relics of a 30 000 year old civilization
Unbelievable power that reduced our moon to rubble
Who are we kidding trying to stand against that no one's taking it seriously
I believe that this temporary peace is going to last forever
So tell me something
What's gonna happen to those poor kids whose heads have been pumped full of nonsense by all us adults
When they face off against those guys biting their time in the wreckage of the moon
What will we say to them when they all start dying because of our lies
Slain princess of salem slain look at me please yes
I have come to say goodbye
It's time for me to make my journey to earth and begin my goodwill visit there
The knowledge you have so generously shared with me is certain to prove of great value
Your highness might it not be dangerous
We cannot live in fear the time is now for someone to take the first step toward creating a lasting peace for all of us
princess
Take this it is an old earth charm that is said to ward off evil spirits
I couldn't you said you got this from your father trust me
He would have wanted it to go to you
I thank you for having saved both of us when we needed it five years ago
please
When I arrive on that beautiful blue planet your prayers of peace will be with me there as well
I
Thank you my friend
Princess of Salem your shuttle is waiting
I must go goodbye be well
Remember who you are you filthy terran
Although I was reluctant to dissuade her highness from her folly remember this
The mess you make is ultimately my responsibility
That is the only warning you shall receive
Yes, sir
You don't hold a favorable opinion of slain either do you adelritzel um
It's not my place
When you really think about it, we are actually descendants from the very emigrants who came from that blue planet
So there is no reason we should have such hatred for them
Begging your pardon, but when emperor verse inherited the authority of aldonoa we became a new and better race
Distinct from the old humanity we left behind on earth
And as the living embodiment of the power of the gods milady those things should not be said
My desire is to reestablish friendly relations with our distant former home
Regardless of circumstances which have caused such strife and separation i am committed to peace
Yes, yes milady
Selina home on transfer orbit complete
Stand by for descent sequence
All we can do now is pray for her safety
Your excellency a message from saws bone castle shall i put it through yes
I expect you'd be rather bored now three months of gentlemanly hosting will no doubt take its toll
I cannot say that i've carried out my duties
Well, this was the last opportunity that I was given to persuade her against making such a trip
You really needn't worry about it if anything bad were to happen to her highness the 37 clans here in orbit would rise as one to wreak their revenge for it
Even the filthy terrans would know that would be the case
One can only hope
But then
If what they actually wanted was to provoke hostilities
That could turn out to be a blessing for us
In a very sad way of course
Sozbo don't say such things oh was that a bit too far
Well, we orbital knights have dwelt in our castles for 15 years since the time of our fathers
Waiting for the day we would reach out and touch that blue radiance
So it's finally happening yeah
Years of laying low down here and this whole thing is finally going to pay off
There they are now just appearing down the boulevard is the convoy of her highness of salem versa lucia the royal princess of mars
Her limousine is proceeding
Oh great we made it in time
Catching it on the news would have been every bit as good
Ah this is supposed to be a goodwill visit remember so we need to join in with everyone to help raise the noise level
Let her know she's welcome you know
When did you switch sides and become a martian sympathizer hey she's royalty a princess
Plus buzz on the net says she's actually pretty cute geez should have known
Huh
Nothing not shocking
It's 200 millimeters of tinted bulletproof glass
That's pretty typical for vip limos these days especially with government vehicles
Isn't she gonna wave to us or something it is a parade right what are you asking me for it's probably a security thing
Then why are we even wasting our time here like this
Ah you're the one who wanted to come here
Oh huh good price on eggs
Always lost in your own little world
Aha was pretty sure i'd find you here
What's up inko you here to see the parade too
No student council the security people wanted some help directing traffic
Well aren't we the little go-getter
Hey if you three aren't doing anything you could help out there's so many people here
I'd use trained monkeys if I had them
Geez thanks
Come on i need some help you know with this guy you might be better off getting the monkey
What come on all you have to do is put on an armband and stand there
I don't know what do you think
What about you inaho will you help me
We need to leave now
Missiles are on the way
What was that?
What's going on?
It made it through
The umo got past the blast
Now
We know what yeah
wait
Our princess of Salem's heartfelt wish for planetary peace
has been crushed forever in a despicable act of Terran treachery.
Diverse Empire must bring down the Hammer of Justice
in response to this atrocity committed by old humanity.
Hear me, Knights of Mars.
No more will we sit idly waiting.
It is time to put into motion the grand task of a generation,
the Earthfall Operation.
Count Cruteo, sir. Reactor output is at 97%. Launch preparations complete.
I am solely to blame for not stopping the Princess from going to Earth.
Do not fall behind the others.
It's come to this. We shall use force to show our grief.
Landing Castle, descend!
Our target's Japan!
Princess.
Of the 37 landing castles which were in orbit,
we confirmed there are 19 approaching.
Projected landing points are coming in now.
New Orleans, Beijing, Mozambique, and also Tokyo.
That's so lame.
These guys are spreading themselves way too thin.
They're only interested in the landing.
There's no command structure.
Shows just how little you know.
Lieutenant!
They don't want or need a command structure.
They're 37 different forces led by 37 different Knights.
Every one of them wants to be the first to land so he can be king of the hill.
Their rivals are their fellow Mars Knights.
They were never concerned about counterattacks from the surface.
If that's true, they would go as far as breaking the ceasefire?
Ceasefire?
For the past 15 years,
they've never stopped fighting a war up there in the wreckage of the moon.
A war.
To live another day.
To fight.
Get it in gear already.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
What's that up there?
I say cry, yeah.
It's a step in time.
What's so sad?
Let them pass this path.
Let them be good by outside and feel it.
Hey, sis!
Look at the shooting stars!
Wow, you're right.
There's so many of them.
Did you remember to make a wish?
Yes!
I wish that people all over the world would just get along and be happy.
Yeah?
Yeah!
Alright.
Well, please.
Sorry.
I didn't know that I heard people all over you.
With some signs of this,
I'll beетровí.
shoot.
Oh, you're right.
You're right again.
Sorry.
I didn't know that I should admit.
That's true.
It's true.
Oh, if my Jesuco,
that hint makes my wish,
it doesn'tajo demê.
Oh, you're right.
so
me
Thank you.